<resources>
<string name="debughint">
This program helps you to test alarms.
Click Menu to see the available options.
See the file /menu/main_menu.xml to find what each menu does.
\n\nVarious menu items allow you to set alarms.
\n\nSee the LogCat to see messages from the receivers that respond to these alarms
\n\nSome debug messages will appear on this activity here, but for the rest you 
have to see the logcat.
</string>

<string name="alarmonce_message">
\n\n
Fire an alarm once.
See the LogCat for a response in 30 seconds. 
Implemented in file SendAlarmOnceTester.java.
\n\nSchdeduling alarm at: %s 
</string>

<string name="alarmrepeated_message">
\n\n
Fire an alarm repeatedly.
See the LogCat for a response in 30 seconds. 
Alarm will repeat every 5 secs after that. 
Implemented in file SendRepatingAlarmTester.java
\n\nSchdeduling Repeating alarm in 5 sec interval starting at:%s  
</string>

<string name="alarm_cancel_message">
\n\n
Cancel the repeating Alarm.
See the logcat and see that the repeating alarm has stopped. 
Implemented in file CancelRepeatingAlarmTester.java.
</string>

<string name="alarm_multiples_message">
Schedule the same intent multiple times. 
Only the last one takes effect. 
Implemented in file ScheduleIntentMultipleTimesTester.java
\n\nSchdeduling alarms at:%s  
</string>

<string name="distinctalarms_message">
\n\n
Scheduling a series of 4 distinct alarms with the same intent. 
The intent will be made distinct using the request id. 
See the logcat for messages from each of the alarms. 
You may want to cancel the previous alarms using the cancel alarms menu item.
\n\nAlarms set to go off at:%s
</string>

<string name="intentprimacy_message">
\n\n
If you schedule an alarm multiple times on the same intent
the last alarm will override the previous ones. 
In this example a single shot alarm overrides the repeating alarm
when set on the same intent. See logcat that you won\'t see the
repeating alarm but gets fired only once. 
\n\nSchdeduling Repeating alarm in 5 sec interval starting at: %s
</string>

</resources>
